<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mischa Friegang</title>
    <link>http://www.mischaf.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mischa Friegang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:59:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mischaf.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Wireguard CGNAT Traversal Setup</title>
      <link>http://www.mischaf.com/posts/wireguard_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 11:47:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mischaf.com/posts/wireguard_setup/</guid>
      <description>Where I live there are essentially 2 options for(usable in this day and age) internet, you go with one of the local WISPs, or you use LTE in some form. The latter of the 2 is what I have ended up with after a few years of spotty and slow sevice with 2 different WISPs. It has some limitations, but I&amp;rsquo;m able to get 40-50Mbps down and 10-15Mbps up consistently. Someday Elon Musk and Starlink will save me, but for now it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.mischaf.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:59:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mischaf.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This website is a place for me to blog(occasionally) about things that interest me, and hopefully share them with people who are interested in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desolation Wilderness North Lakes Tour</title>
      <link>http://www.mischaf.com/posts/desolation_north_lakes_tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:52:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mischaf.com/posts/desolation_north_lakes_tour/</guid>
      <description>June 27th, 2020 My Dad, Jed and I went on this hike with the intention of doing a shakedown overnight trip to test our legs and gear for our upcoming PCT section hike. We arrived at the trail head at 7:30 that morning and started towards the Forni lake trail with plenty of mosquitoes to keep us company. The first leg of the journey was fairly uneventful, I’ve hiked to Forni lake probably a dozen times or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://www.mischaf.com/posts/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:47:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mischaf.com/posts/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>Hello from my first Hugo Post. This marks the start of the process of migrating away from Wordpress to something more lightweight. Lots of cleanup and tweaking to do&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>